[{"question":"Who does Mario save?","answers":["Sonic","Princess Peach","John Cena"],"rightAns":"Princess Peach","qid":"1","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What is arachnophobia?","answers":["Fear of spiders","Fear of bears","Fear of your parents"],"rightAns":"Fear of spiders","qid":"2","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"When was the battle of hastings?","answers":["1914","1066","2020"],"rightAns":"1066","qid":"3","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"Which is a dance in the game fortnite?","answers":["The waltz","The floss","The duggy"],"rightAns":"The floss","qid":"4","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"How many pairs of ribs would the normal human have?","answers":["10","12","14"],"rightAns":"12","qid":"5","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"If you subtract the number of sides on a heptagon from the number of sides on a dodecagon what answer do you get?","answers":["3","4","5"],"rightAns":"5","qid":"6","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"Which is the fighter created in UK?","answers":["Bf109","Spitfire","P-51"],"rightAns":"Spitfire","qid":"7","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"Which medium does sound travel faster?","answers":["Air","Water","Solid"],"rightAns":"Solid","qid":"8","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"The French number 'neuf' is what in English?","answers":["19","9","7"],"rightAns":"9","qid":"9","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"Which number lies directly opposite the number three on a standard die?","answers":["4","5","2"],"rightAns":"4","qid":"10","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What is the largest US state by size?","answers":["Texas","Californa","New Mexico"],"rightAns":"Texas","qid":"11","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"Who created Facebook?","answers":["Mark Zuckerberg","Peter Jones","Tom Anderson"],"rightAns":"Mark Zuckerberg","qid":"12","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What colour to do you get when you mix red and white?","answers":["Red","Pink","White"],"rightAns":"Pink","qid":"13","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0}]